In this video we're going to begin our discussion of run time systems. Now, at
在这段视频中，我们将开始讨论运行时系统。现在，在
this point we have actually covered the entire front end of the compiler which
这一点我们实际上已经涵盖了编译器的整个前端，
consists of the three phases, lexical analysis, parsing and semantic analysis
包括词法分析、句法分析和语义分析三个阶段
And these three passes or these three phases together, their job is to really
而这三关或者这三个阶段加在一起，他们的工作就是真正
enforce the language semantics or the language definition. So, we know. After
强制执行语言语义或语言定义。所以，我们知道。之后
these three phases are done that if no errors have been generated by anyone of
这三个阶段在以下情况下进行：如果以下任何人都没有生成错误
those phases then the program is actually a valid program in the programming
这些阶段则程序实际上是编程中的有效程序
language that we're compiling And at this point the compiler is going to be able to
我们正在编译的语言，在这一点上，编译器将能够
produce codes to produce a translation of the program that you can actually execute.
生成代码以生成您可以实际执行的程序的翻译。
And I should say that of course. Enforcing the language definition is just one
当然，我应该这么说。强制执行语言定义只是其中之一
purpose of the front-end. The front-end also builds the data structures that are
前端的用途。前端还构建以下数据结构
needed to do co-generation as we seen but there is a real. Once we get through the
就像我们看到的那样，需要做热电联产，但有一个真正的。一旦我们通过了
front-end we no longer looking for errors in the program. We're no longer trying to
前端我们不再寻找程序中的错误。我们不再试图
figure out whether it's a valid program. Now we're really down to the point where
找出它是否是一个有效的程序。现在我们真的到了这样一个地步
we're going to generate code And that is a job at the back end. So cogeneration is
我们要生成代码，这是后端的工作。所以热电联产是
certainly part of it. The other big part of the back end is program optimization so
当然是其中的一部分。后端的另一个重要部分是程序优化，因此
doing transformations to improve the program. But before we can talk about
进行转换以改进程序。但在我们谈到
either one of those things, we need to talk about Runtime organization And why is
这两件事中的任何一件，我们都需要讨论运行时组织，为什么
that, well because we need to understand what it is we're trying to generate before
这是因为我们需要了解我们之前想要产生的是什么
we can talk about how we generated and have that makes sense. So first, we're
我们可以谈谈我们是如何产生和拥有的，这是有意义的。所以首先，我们要
gonna talk about what the, the translator program looks like and how it's organized
我要谈谈翻译程序是什么样子的，以及它是如何组织的
and then we'll talk about algorithms and code generation algorithms were actually
然后我们将讨论算法和代码生成算法
producing those things. And this is a well-understood area or at least some very
生产那些东西。这是一个广为人知的地区，或者至少是一些非常
standard techniques that are widely used and those are the ones we wanted to cover
广泛使用的标准技术，这些都是我们想要介绍的技术
and, and encourage you to use in your project. The main thing we're going to
并鼓励您在您的项目中使用。我们要做的主要事情是
cover in this sequence of videos is the management of Runtime resources and in
本系列视频的内容包括运行时资源的管理和
particular I'm going to be stressing the correspondence and the distinction between
我将特别强调两者之间的对应和区别
static and dynamic structures. So static structures are things that exist to
静电和动态结构。所以静电结构是存在于
compile time and dynamic structures, those are the things that exist or happen at
编译时和动态结构，这些都是存在或发生在
Runtime And, this is probably the most important distinction for you to try to
运行时，这可能是您要尝试的最重要的区别
understand if you really want to understand how a compiler works. What
如果您真的想了解编译器是如何工作的，请理解。什么
happens to the compile time and what happens at run time. Having a clear
发生在编译时和运行时发生的事情。有一个清晰的
separation in your mind between what is done by the compiler and what is deferred
在您的脑海中区分编译器所做的工作和被延迟的工作
to when the target program or the generated program actually runs that is
设置为目标程序或生成的程序实际运行的时间，即
key to really understanding how compilers work. And we'll also be talking about
真正理解编译器如何工作的关键。我们还将讨论
storage organization. So how memory is used to store the data structures of the
存储组织。那么如何使用内存来存储
executing program. So let's begin at the beginning. So initially there is the
正在执行程序。那么让我们从头开始吧。所以最初有一个
operating system and the operating system is the only thing that is running on the
操作系统，而操作系统是唯一运行在
machine and when a program is invoke. When the user says he wants to run a program,
机器以及当程序被调用时。当用户说他想要运行程序时，
what happens while the operating system is going to allocate space for the program
当操作系统要为程序分配空间时会发生什么
the code for the program is going to be loaded into that space and then the
该程序的代码将被加载到该空间中，然后
operating system is going to execute a job to the entry point or the main function of
操作系统将执行作业到入口点或主函数
the program and then your program will be off and running. So, let's take a look at
该程序，然后您的程序将关闭并运行。那么我们来看一下，
what the organization memory looks like very roughly when the Operating System
当操作系统运行时，组织内存大致是什么样子
began execution of the compiled program. So we're gonna draw our pictures of memory
开始执行编译后的程序。所以我们要画一幅记忆的图画
like this. That would be just a big block and there will be a starting address at
像这样。那将只是一个很大的挡路，并且将有一个开始地址在
the, a lower address and a higher address and this is all the memory that is
一个较低的地址和一个较高的地址，这就是
allocated to your program. Now into some portion of that space goes to code for the
分配给您的程序。现在进入该空间的某一部分，转到
program so the actual compiled code for the program is loaded usually at one end
程序，因此程序的实际编译代码通常在一端加载
of the memory space allocated to the program. And then there is a bunch. Of
分配给程序的内存空间的大小。然后还有一堆。的
other space that is going to be used for other things and we'll talk about that in
其他空间将用于其他用途，我们将在
a minute. Before going on, I want to say a few words about this pictures of Run-time
稍等片刻。在继续之前，我想就这张运行时图片说几句话
Organization because I'm going to be drawing a lot of them over the next few
因为在接下来的几年里我会画很多这样的照片
videos. So, it's just traditional to have memory drawn as a rectangle with the low
视频。因此，传统的做法是将内存绘制为带有低位的矩形
address at the top and the high address at the bottom. There's nothing magic about
地址在顶部，高位地址在底部。没有什么神奇之处
that, just a convention we could adjust it easily every verse or order of the
这只是一种惯例，我们可以很容易地调整它的每一节或每一个顺序
address, no big deal. And then we'll be drawing lines to the limit different
地址，没什么大不了的。然后我们会把线画到不同的极限
regions of this memory showing different kinds of data and how they're stored in
显示不同类型数据以及它们在中的存储方式的内存区域
the memory allocated to the program. And clearly these pictures are simplifications
分配给程序的内存。很明显，这些图片是简单化的
if this, is a virtual memory system for example, there's no guarantee that these
例如，如果这是一个虚拟内存系统，就不能保证这些
data is actually laid out contiguously but it helps to understand you know, what the
数据实际上是连续布局的，但它有助于理解
different kinds of data are. And what the, a compiler needs to do with them to have
不同种类的数据是相同的。编译器需要对它们做什么才能拥有
simple pictures like this. So coming back to our picture of run time organization,
像这样简单的图片。所以回到我们对运行时组织的描述上来，
we have some block memory and the first portion of that is occupied by the actual
我们有一些挡路内存，其中的第一部分被实际的
generated code for the program and then there was this other space and we're what
为程序生成代码，然后有另一个空间，我们是什么
goes to that space? Well, what goes to that space is the data for the program. So
去那个地方吗？进入那个空间的是程序的数据。所以
all the data is in the rest of the space and the tricky thing about code generation
所有的数据都在睡觉的空间里，代码生成的棘手之处在于
that the compiler is responsible for generating the code but it's also
编译器负责生成代码，但它也
responsible for orchestrating the data. So the compiler has to decide what the lay of
负责编排数据。所以编译器必须决定哪一层
the data is going to be and then generate code that correctly manipulates that data
数据将被转换，然后生成正确操作该数据的代码
so there are references of course in the code. To the data and the code and data
所以代码中当然有引用。数据、代码和数据
need to be designed, the code and the layout of the data, excuse me, need to be
需要设计的，代码和数据的布局，打扰一下，需要
designed together so that the generated program will function correctly. Now, it
一起设计，以便生成的程序能够正常运行。现在，它
turns out that this actually more than one kind of data that the compiler is going to
事实证明，这实际上不只是编译器要处理的一种数据
be interested in and what we'll be talking about. In the next video is the different
对我们将要谈论的内容感兴趣。下一个视频中的不同之处在于
kinds of data and the different distinction between the kinds of data that
数据类型和数据类型之间的不同区别
go in this data area.
进入这个数据区。